Guide to the Stanford University, Vice President for Business Affairs, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Reis, William D., Santa Margarita Ranch, Water, 1971-1975 (Box 72, Folder 16)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Reis,William D., Santa Margarita Ranch, Exhibits - Easements, 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Richfield Oil Co. - Airplane, Document 1459, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Richman, Frederick I. (Consolidated Mortgage Co.), 1968-1971 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- Gifts, Miscellaneous - Wingfield, George, 1962-1964 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Gilman Street - 604 - Palo Alto Owned Property (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Gilman Street - 604 - Rental File, 1953-1962 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Girl Scouts, 1962-1964 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Girschick, Meyer, 1948-1962 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Golden Nugget Analysis, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 30)
- Golf Course Improvements, (886), 1974-1975 (Box 108, Folder 32)
- Gotelli, George - Lease, 1965-1967 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Gotelli, George A. - Flower Grower, 1953-1967 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Governor's Ave. Subdivision, 1949-1951 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Governor's Lane Complex - Budget & Fiscal, 734, 1972-1977 (Box 106, Folder 3)
- Governor's Lane Complex - Bulletins, Supplements, 734, 1974-1975 (Box 106, Folder 9)
- Governor's Lane Complex - Change Orders, Bulletins, File #1, 1974-1975 (Box 106, Folder 5)
- Governor's Lane Complex - Construction Management, 734, 1973 (Box 106, Folder 12)
- Governor's Lane Complex - Contract Changes, 734, 1974-1975 (Box 106, Folder 8)
- Governor's Lane Complex - Exhibits, 734, (empty folder) (Box 106, Folder 16)
- Governor's Lane Complex - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, 734, 1974-1975 (Box 106, Folder 10)
- Governor's Lane Complex - Field Meetings, 734, 1974-1975 (Box 106, Folder 15)
- Governor's Lane Complex - Field Orders, 734, 1974 (Box 106, Folder 13)
- Governor's Lane Complex - General Correspondence #2, 734, 1974-1976 (Box 106, Folder 6)
- Governor's Lane Complex - General Correspondence, 734, 1972-1974 (Box 106, Folder 7)
- Governor's Lane Complex - Soils Reports, 1973 (Box 106, Folder 11)
- Governor's Lane Complex - Testing Laboratory Reports, 1973-1975 (Box 106, Folder 14)
- Graduate School of Business - Admissions Office Remodel, 909, 1974-1975 (Box 103, Folder 33)
- Graduate School of Business - Air Conditioning, 1966-1968 (Box 116, Folder 6)
- Graduate School of Business - Change Orders, 1964-1966 (Box 116, Folder 9)
- Graduate School of Business - Construction Reports, 1964-1966 (Box 116, Folder 18)
- Graduate School of Business - Disbursements, File I, 1960-1965 (Box 116, Folder 5)
- Graduate School of Business - Disbursements, File II, 1965-1967 (Box 116, Folder 4)
- Graduate School of Business - Exhibits (Box 117, Folder 6)
- Graduate School of Business - Field Insp. Prog. Reports, File I, 1964-1965 (Box 116, Folder 16)
- Graduate School of Business - Field Insp. Prog. Reports, File II, 1965-1966 (Box 116, Folder 15)
- Graduate School of Business - Field Insp. Prog. Reports, File III, 1966-1967 (Box 116, Folder 14)
- Graduate School of Business - General Correspondence, File I, 1960-1964 (Box 117, Folder 4)
- Graduate School of Business - General Correspondence, File II, 1964-1965 (Box 117, Folder 3)
- Graduate School of Business - General Correspondence, File III, 1966 (Box 117, Folder 2)
- Graduate School of Business - General Correspondence, File IV, 1966-1968 (Box 117, Folder 1)
- Graduate School of Business - Grant Application, 1965 (Box 116, Folder 7)
- Graduate School of Business - Legal Documents, 1960-1967 (Box 116, Folder 8)
- Graduate School of Business - Supplements, 1964-1966 (Box 116, Folder 17)
- Graduate School of Business - Testing Reports, Folder I, 1961-1965 (Box 116, Folder 13)
- Graduate School of Business - Testing Reports, Folder II, 1965 (Box 116, Folder 12)
- Graduate School of Business - Testing Reports, Folder III, 1965-1966 (Box 116, Folder 11)
- Graduate School of Business - Testing Reports, Folder IV, 1966 (Box 116, Folder 10)
- Graduate School of Business Jackson Library Alterations, 910, 1974-1975 (Box 103, Folder 34)
- Gray, H. D. - 612 Alvarado, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Greer, John, 1947-1950 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Grounds Maintenance, 1971-1974 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- GT & E Bldg. (D.C. Power) Alterations for Stanford Drug Education Program, (900), 1974-1975 (Box 108, Folder 28)
- Guerard, A. L. Mrs., 1933-1961 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Hacienda, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Hale Bros, Inc., 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Hale Bros, Inc., 1945-1958 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Hall, Darrell - Darrell’s Auto Upholstering Company, 2490 El Camino Real, 1955-1967 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Hall, John E., 1959-1961 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Hanan, Patrick, 1959-1968 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Hanker, Fred Charles Mrs., 1940-1962 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Hansen, William W., 1940-1950 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Harrer, G. A., 1957-1960 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Harriman, Raymond Davis, 1954-1964 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Harsh, Philip W., 1957-1960 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Harvard Street Properties (College Terrace) - 2128, 2130, 2140 Harvard St., 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Haseltine, Miss Orre - Carmen Valley Property, 1960-1961 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Haynie, Thomas G. & Helen Adele, 1952-1960 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Health Service - Documents, 1962-1972 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Health Service, #1, 1957-1963 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Health Service, #3, 1966-1969 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- HEPL - Stage I - Exhibits (Box 13, Folder 4)
- HEPL - Stage II - Contract Changes, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- HEPL - Stage II - Phase A - Exhibits (Box 14, Folder 3)
- HEPL - Stage II - Phase A & B - Correspondence, File I, 1966-1969 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- HEPL - Stage II - Phase C - Change Orders, Supplements, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- HEPL - Stage II - Phase C - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- HEPL - Stage II - Phase C - Disbursements, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- HEPL - Stage II - Phase C - Exhibits (Box 14, Folder 10)
- HEPL - Stage II - Phase C - Field Inspector Progress Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- HEPL - Stage II - Phase C - Legal, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- HEPL - Stage II - Phases A - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, #1, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- HEPL - Stage II - Phases A & B - Correspoondence, #3, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- HEPL - Stage II - Phases A & B - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, #2, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- HEPL - Stage II - Phases A & B - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, #3, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- HEPL - Stage II - Phases A & B - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, #4, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- HEPL - Stage II - Testing Lab Reports, File No. 5, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- HEPL (High Energy Physics Laboratory) - Stage II - Phase A & B - Correspondence, File II, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- HEPL [High Energy Physics Laboratory] Tunnel - Stage I - Progress Reports and Architects Reports, File I, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- HEPL [High Energy Physics Laboratory] Tunnel - Stage I - Testing Lab Reports, File II, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- HEPL End Station 2 - Fan Access Platform, 841, 1974-1975 (Box 109, Folder 8)
- HEPL Expansion - Stage II - Phase A - Testing Laboratory Reports, III, 1967-1969 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- HEPL Expansion - Stage II - Phase A & B - Supplements, #1, 1968-1970 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- HEPL Expansion - Stage II - Phase A & B - Testing Laboratory Reports, IV, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- HEPL Expansion - Stage II - Phases A & B - Disbursements, 1966-1971 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- HEPL Expansion - Stage II - Phases A & B - Legal, 1966-1970 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- HEPL Expansion - Stage II - Suplements, #2, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- HEPL Expansion - Tunnel Liner, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- HEPL Tunnel - Stage I - Change Orders, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- HEPL Tunnel - Stage I - Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- HEPL Tunnel - Stage I - Disbursements, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- HEPL Tunnel - Stage I - Inspector’s Daily Reports & Architect’s Reports, File II, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- HEPL Tunnel - Stage I - Inspector’s Daily Reports & Architect’s Reports, File III, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- HEPL Tunnel - Stage I - Legal, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- HEPL Tunnel - Stage I - Testing Lab Reports, File I, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- HEPL Tunnel - Supplements, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Heron, David W., 1957-1961 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Herrin Basement Completion - Contract Changes, #560, 1970-1971 (Box 112, Folder 10)
- Herrin Basement Completion - Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 112, Folder 11)
- Herrin Basement Completion - Disbursements, 1968-1971 (Box 112, Folder 9)
- Herrin Basement Completion - Exhibits, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 16)
- Herrin Basement Completion - Field Inspector’s Progress Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 112, Folder 14)
- Herrin Basement Completion - Legal, 19668-1972 (Box 112, Folder 8)
- Herrin Basement Completion - Payrolls, 1970-1971 (Box 112, Folder 15)
- Herrin Basement Completion - Supplements, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 12)
- Herrin Basement Completion - Testing Lab. Reports (empty) (Box 112, Folder 13)
- Herrin Laboratories - Exhibits (Box 112, Folder 22)
- Herrin Laboratories (Biology) - Change Orders, #532, 1968 (Box 112, Folder 20)
- Herrin Laboratories (Biology) - Disbrsements, 1968-1969 (Box 112, Folder 18)
- Herrin Laboratories (Biology) - Field Inspector’s Reports, 1968 (Box 112, Folder 21)
- Herrin Laboratories (Biology) - General Correspondence, 1967-1975 (Box 112, Folder 19)
- Herrin Laboratories (Biology) - Legal, 1967-1969 (Box 112, Folder 17)
- Herrin Laboratory Alterations, 762, 1973-1976 (Box 109, Folder 22)
- Hetch Hetchy Water Supply, 1913-1929 (Box 100, Folder 10)
- Hillview Avenue Extension - Changes to Contract, 1963-1964 (Box 102, Folder 31)
- Holden, Paul E. & Laura A., 1951-1959 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Holsti, Rudolph (Mrs.), 1942-1950 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Hoover Herbert, 1942-1948 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Hoover Institution - Agreement with Zawisza, 1958-1959 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Hoover Institution - Contract with Plon Libraire, 1957-1965 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Hoover Institution - Jiji Press Contract, 1957-1960 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Hoover Institution (The Russian Review, Inc.), 1969-1973 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Hoover Institution Basement Renovations - Legal Documents, 419, 1964-1965 (Box 103, Folder 1)
- Hoover, Lou Henry, Building - Legal, 436, 1964-1968 (Box 102, Folder 33)
- Hoover, William G., 1936-1956 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Hopkins, Mrs Timothy, 1941-1942 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Hopkins, Timothy, 1929-1940 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Hopkins, Timothy, 1940-1946 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Hopkins, William S., 1937-1947 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Hosp. - Med. Schl. Job 3 - - Budget and Correspondence, 21, 1957-1958 (Box 114, Folder 10)
- Hosp. - Med. Schl. Job 3 - Contract MR - Western Leadburning Contractors, 16, 1958-1960 (Box 114, Folder 1)
- Hosp. - Med. Schl. Job 3 - Contract MW - Grover Engineers, Inc., 17, 1958-1959 (Box 114, Folder 2)
- Hosp. - Med. Schl. Job 3 - Contract MX - Schlegel Plumbing Contractors, 18, 1958-1960 (Box 114, Folder 3)
- Hosp. - Med. Schl. Job 3 - Edward D. Stone, Progress Reports, 22a, 1957-1959 (Box 114, Folder 8)
- Hosp. - Med. Schl. Job 3 - Edwards basement, Edward D. Stone, 29A, 1959-1960 Hosp. - Med. Schl. Jobs 1, 2, & 3 - Onsite Sanitary & Storm Sewers - Pisano Bros., Inc., 9A, 1958 (Box 114, Folder 4)
- Hosp. - Med. Schl. Job 3 - Edwards Building, Basement Remodeling, 30, 1959-1961 (Box 114, Folder 5)
- Hosp. - Med. Schl. Job 3 - Medical Center Library, 23, 1956-1960 (Box 114, Folder 9)
- Hosp. - Med. Schl. Jobs 1, 2 & 3 - Maurice Sands Interiors, 14, 1958-1959 (Box 114, Folder 6)
- Hosp. - Med. Schl. Jobs 1,2 & 3 - Onsite - Swenson, 9B, 1957-1962 (Box 114, Folder 7)
- Hospital - Correspondence, #3, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Hospital - Correspondence, #4, 1969-1970 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Hospital - Correspondence, #5, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Hospital - Correspondence, #6, 1967-1969 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Hospital - Medical School - 25, Job 1 - Budget and Correspondence, 1959 (Box 113, Folder 36)
- Hospital - Medical School - Change Orders, 26, Job 3, 1958-1960 (Box 85, Folder 31)
- Hospital - Medical School - Change Orders, Correspondence, 26A, Job3, 1958-1959 (Box 85, Folder 32)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract A, 1, Job 1 - Carl N. Swenson Co., Inc, 1957-1961 (Box 113, Folder 14)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract C, 3, Job 1 - C. L. Frost, 1957-1961 (Box 113, Folder 15)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract E, 5, Job 1 - Fire Protection Products Co., 1957-1959 (Box 113, Folder 16)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract F, 6, Job 1 - Rothschild, Raffin & Weirick, 1957-1960 (Box 113, Folder 17)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract G, 7, Job 1 - A. E. Knowles Corporation, 1957-1960 (Box 113, Folder 18)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract H, 8, Job 1 - Merner Lumber Company, 1957-1960 (Box 113, Folder 19)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract J, 9, Job 1 - The Brookman Co., Inc., 1957-1960 (Box 113, Folder 20)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract K, 10, Job 1 - Selectile Co., Inc., 1957-1960 (Box 113, Folder 21)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract L, 11, Job 1 - P. Grassi - American Terrazzo Co., 1957-1960 (Box 113, Folder 22)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract M, 12, Job 1 - James A. Smith Co., 1957-1960 (Box 113, Folder 23)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract MA, 1, Job 3 - Carl N. Swenson Co., Inc., 1958-1960 (Box 113, Folder 37)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract MB, 2, Job 3 - Romak Iron Works, Inc., 1958-1960 (Box 113, Folder 38)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract MD, 4, Job 3 - Truscon Div., Repulic Steel Corp., 1958-1960 (Box 113, Folder 39)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract ME, 5, Job 3 - Fire Protection Products Co., 1958-1960 (Box 113, Folder 40)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract MF-11, 6A, Job 3 - Weber Showcase, 1958-1960 (Box 113, Folder 42)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract MF, 6, Job 3 - Rothschild, Raffin & Weirick, 1958-1960 (Box 113, Folder 41)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract MG, 7, Job 3 - Floyd T. Bridges Co., 1958-1960 (Box 113, Folder 43)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract MH, 8, Job 3 - Merner Lumber Co., 1958-1960 (Box 113, Folder 44)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract MJ, 9, Job 3 - Western Asbestos Co., 1958-1960 (Box 113, Folder 45)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract ML, 11, Job 3 - National Tile & Terrazzo Co., 1958-1960 (Box 113, Folder 46)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract MM, 12, Job 3 - James A. Smith (Box 113, Folder 47)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract MN, 13, Job 3 - Cobbledick-Kibbe Glass Co., 1958-1959 (Box 113, Folder 48)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract MO, 14, Job 3 - Elevator Maintenance Co., 1958-1960 (Box 113, Folder 49)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract MP, 15, Job 3 - Kenneth C. Sanders & Sons, 1958-1960 (Box 113, Folder 50)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract N, 13, Job 1 - Acme Glass Co., 1957-1960 (Box 113, Folder 24)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract O, 14, Job 1 - Otis Elevator Co., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 25)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract P, 15, Job 1 - W. G. Thompson, 1957-1960 (Box 113, Folder 26)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract Q, 16, Job 1 - The Peele Co., 1957-1960 (Box 113, Folder 27)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract R, 17, Job 1 - Western Leadburning Co., 1957-1960 (Box 113, Folder 28)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract S, 18, Job 1 - General Electric Co. - X-Ray Dept., 1957-1960 (Box 113, Folder 29)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract T, 19, Job 1 - American Sterilizer Co., 1957-1960 (Box 113, Folder 30)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract U, 20, Job 1 - Dohrmann Hotel Supply Co., 1957-1960 (Box 113, Folder 31)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract V, 21, Job 1 - Plibrico Sales & Service Co., 1957 (Box 113, Folder 32)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract W, 22, Job 1 - Grover Engineers, 1957-1960 (Box 113, Folder 33)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract X, 23, Job 1 - Scott Co. (Box 113, Folder 34)
- Hospital - Medical School - Contract Y, 24, Job 1 - Marshall Electric Co., 1957-1961 (Box 113, Folder 35)
- Hospital - Medical School - Equipment, 25, Job 3, 1957-1960 (Box 85, Folder 29)
- Hospital - Medical School - Miscellaneous, 24, Job 3, 1957-1960 (Box 85, Folder 30)
- Hospital - Medical School - Moving Medical School & Library, 28, 1958-1961 (Box 113, Folder 11)
- Hospital - Society of Hospital Attorneys (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Hospital #7, 1969-1972 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Hospital #8, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Hospital Correspondence #1, 1968, some 1971 (Box 85, Folder 28)
- Hospital Correspondence #2, 1968-1969 (Box 85, Folder 27)
- Hospital Expansion (Final Acctg. & Audit), 1976 (Box 33, Folder 33)
- Hospital Expansion Phase I (Facilities, Planning), 1972-1973 (Box 93, Folder 11)
- Hospital Expansion Phase I (Facilities, Planning), 1973 (Box 93, Folder 10)
- Hospital Expansion Phase I (Facilities, Planning), 1974-1976 (Box 93, Folder 9)
- Hospital Expansion Phase I (Facilities, Planning), 1976 (Box 93, Folder 8)
- Hospital Expansion Phase I (Facilities, Planning), 1976-1978 (Box 93, Folder 7)
- Hospital Expansion Phase I, 1972-1976 (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Hospital Expansion Phase I, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 12)
- Hospital Expansion Phase I, 1976 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- Hospital Expansion Phase I, 1976 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Hospital Expansion Phase I, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 13)
- Hospital Linen Service Contingency Plan, 1974 (Binder) (Box 33)
- Hospital Service, 1949-1956 (Box 85, Folder 34)
- Hospital Utility - Tax Information, 1955-1956 (Box 85, Folder 33)
- Housing - Campus Land Leases, 1953-1954 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Housing - Faculty/Staff, #1, 1966-1968 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Housing - Faculty/Staff, #2, 1968-1969 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Housing - Fraternity Cluster - Fire Regulations, Reports, etc., 1962-1969 (Box 73, Folder 13)
- Housing - Fraternity Cluster - Indenture, 1964-1971 (Box 73, Folder 14)
- Housing - Fraternity Cluster - Loan Agreement, Group III, 1965-1973 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Housing - Fraternity Cluster - Loan Application, Group III, 1963-1974 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Housing - Fraternity Cluster - Loan Application, Groups I and II, 1958-1974 (Box 73, Folder 15)
- Housing - Fraternity Cluster - Summer Operations, 1963-1966 (Box 73, Folder 10)
- Housing - Fraternity Cluster - Utilities, 1960-1963 (Box 73, Folder 12)
- Housing - Fraternity Cluster - Utilities, Exhibits (Box 73, Folder 11)
- Housing - Fraternity Letter Agreement, 1965-1970 (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Housing - Low Income - Ad Hoc Housing Advisory Committee Minutes, 1969-1970 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Housing - Low Income - Exhibits (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Housing - Low Income - Jr. Faculty/Staff, 1967-1970 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Housing - Low Income - Walker Subcommittee Minutes, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Housing - Low Income (Newspaper Clippings)1968-1970 (Box 73, Folder 28)
- Housing - Low Income, I, 1968-1969 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Housing - Low Income, II, 1969-1970 (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Housing - Low Income, III, 1970 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Housing - Low Income, IV, 1970-1971 (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Housing - Low Income, VA, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 16)
- Housing - Low Income, VB, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 17)
- Housing - Residences - Branner, 1963-1970 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Housing - Residences - Coeducational, 1962-1970 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Housing - Residences - Crothers Memorial, 1956-1972 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Housing - Residences - Crothers, 1961-1970 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Housing - Residences - Escondido V - Loan and financing - Recommendation and supporting analy., 1970-1971 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Housing - Residences - Escondido Village - General, 1965-1971 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Housing - Residences - Escondido Village - Indenture, 1959-1971 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Housing - Residences - Escondido Village - Loan Application, 1970-1971 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- Housing - Residences - Escondido Village - Loan Application, 1971-1972 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Housing - Residences - Escondido Village - Power Outage, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Housing - Residences - Excondido Village - Programming, 1960-1971 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- Housing - Residences - Graduate Student Housing Project, 1964-1969 (Box 53, Folder 16)
- Housing - Residences - Interior Decoration, 1954-1968 (Box 53, Folder 17)
- Housing - Residences - Lagunita Court, 1948-1970 (Box 53, Folder 18)
- Housing - Residences - Lasuen Houses, 1945-1966 (Box 53, Folder 19)
- Housing - Residences - Law School (Planning), 1964-1965 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Housing - Residences - Manzanita Park, 1970-1971 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Housing - Residences - Men, 1965-1966 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Housing - Residences - Planning, 1962-1971 (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Housing - Residences - Proposals (Townhouses), 1968-1969 (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Housing - Residences - Rates #2, 1970-1972 (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Housing - Residences - Rates, #1, 1951-1969 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Housing - Residences - Roble, 1960-1971 (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Housing - Residences - Senior Persons, Administration, 1959-1966 (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Housing - Residences - Stanford Village - Disposition of Property - Exhibits (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Housing - Residences - Stanford Village - Disposition of Property, 1966-1970 (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Housing - Residences - Stanford Village - Disposition of Property, #1, 1957-1962 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Housing - Residences - Stanford Village - Disposition of Property, #2, 1963-1966 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Housing - Residences - Stanford Village - Maps (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Housing - Residences - Stanford Village - Menlo Park School Dist., 1947-1960 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Housing - Residences - Stanford Village - Miscellaneous, 1946-1968 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Housing - Residences - Stanford Village - Stanford Research Institute - Steam Heat Agreements, 1957-1965 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Housing - Residences - Stanford Village - Stanford Research Institute, 1951-1961 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Housing - Residences - Stanford Village - Stanford Research Institute, 1961-1969 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Housing - Residences - Stanford Village - Tax Matters, 1946-1958 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Housing - Residences - Stanford Village - U.S. Geolog. Survey, 1954-1958 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Housing - Residences - Stanford Village - Utilities, 1948-1966 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Housing - Residences - Stern, 1963-1971 (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Housing - Residences - Study of Residential Life 1971 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Housing - Residences - Telephones, 1960-1968 (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Housing - Residences - Toyon, 1962-1971 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Housing - Residences - Wilbur, 1964-1971 (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Housing - Residences - Women’s, 1947-1967 (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Housing - Residences -Moore, Florence, 1955-1973 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Housing - Residences and Food Service - Major Repairs & Replacements, 1965-1971 (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Housing - Residences, 1966-1973 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Housing on Stanford Lands (Box 89, Folder 3)
- HUD Moratorium - Frenchman’s Terrace, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 20)
- HUD/Urban Coalition Correspondence re Economic Mix, Priorities, 1972-1975 (Box 95, Folder 14)
- Humanities & Sciences Space Renovations, Building 120 - Disbursements, 1972-1974 (Box 115, Folder 3)
- Hunt, Andrew D., 1958-1964 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Hunter, Robert L., 1963-1966 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Ike, Nobutaka, 1950-1960 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Income Tax, 1931-1937 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Incorporation, 1951-1967 (Box 51, Folder 18)
- Industrial Area - Correspondence on Other Developments, 1953-1973 (Box 51, Folder 19)
- Industrial Area - LM-5 - Maximum Buildable Area Studies, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 24)
- Industrial Area - LM-5 (Coyote Hill) - Public Relations and Newspapers, 1969-1973 (Box 51, Folder 22)
- Industrial Area - LM-5 (Coyote Hill), 1969 (Box 51, Folder 20)